[Disclaimer:
All depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
Do not disappear on me again.
And do not get yourself hurt.
Get your act together soon.
Take them away!
- Don't hurt Jam!
- Let me go!
- Stop!
- Jam!
Hey, be gentle!
The kid's this tiny!
- Hey!
I was too lazy to go into town,
so I asked some locals
if I could stay here for the night.
Someday... you will find someone you love
who loves you back.
Mr. Sarm.
Here.
What nonsense did you get yourself into?
A weaver ant nest fell on me.
I came across a mango tree,
and the mangoes looked tasty, so...
I picked a few.
Here.
What do you think?
But mango trees
are not usually free for the taking.
I've looked around.
The tree's pretty isolated.
No one should see me do it.
You thief.
You deserved to get bitten by
a swarm of weaver ants.
Oh...
Let's leave already.
Come on.
Take it slow.
Ow...
Here.
Easy, please.
It hurts.
Hop on my back.
Hm?
Hmm?
Hey!
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself,
not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space
when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart,
lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
No need to sneak a peek.
Come sit with me.
Be careful when you walk.
Right.
Come.
Go ahead and sit.
Thank you.
How are you feeling?
Is your fever gone?
It is, actually.
Despite being this tiny,
you're one tough cookie.
Do say no sometimes
when Sib gives you a task.
I cannot do that.
This is my job, after all.
Right.
How has working under Sib been?
Hm? Has it been good?
It has been fun.
It is like playing a game.
How?
Well, I am given a task, correct?
Uh-huh.
Upon completion, I will go...
Yay!
Hm?
Mission complete.
Gosh.
What a kid.
And is this task
the toughest of them all?
Mhm.
It seems like when I started this game,
I may have chosen Hardcore difficulty.
Do you want to give up, though?
Not at all.
I will just keep
being a burden to you like this.
Hm?
Snoop,
did you ask if I wanted that?
By the way, why the name "Jam"?
Your mom a fan of Neko Jump?
Otosan,
my father...
Right...
He gave me a name that
sounds like my cousin's name, Nei.
Oh.
What about your name?
It's dead simple.
I have two siblings,
and I'm the third child.
You do not consider Sib one of you?
Of course, I do.
But if we're talking about the same mother,
there are only three of us.
You already know that
my father
has had so many affairs.
I've lost count of how many there are.
Sib walked his own path.
The same goes for Namnueng
and Song.
Our parents went their own way, too.
That's why
I don't want to be with my family.
So I chose to go far away
when I was heartbroken.
Even though I seem so cheerful,
I do get lonely.
It is okay.
Once you get back home,
I will create a Tinder account for you.
Paint thinner is my forte.
That is why you are always this high.
Right.
You're not wrong.
Honestly,
we've been through so much together.
How about we become friends?
Would that be a good idea?
I am way younger than you.
I cannot treat you like a friend, can I?
Oh, how about this?
Just ignore the fact that I'm almost 30
and you're only 23.
How does that sound?
Are you serious?
Mm.
Feel free to be yourself with me.
Sure.
Mm.
Let me ask you something, then...
What?
Why the hell did you leave your job behind?
Huh?
Just kidding.
That's a bit harsh.
It's starting to get cold lying here.
Hm?
Hug me, please?
Well, you are lying there shirtless.
So cold.
Can I have a hug?
Do you want to use this, then?
I don't want it.
A hug, please.
Will you?
Please?
It's so cold.
Hurry up, please?
I'm freezing.
Just look at the way you dress.
Just a bit more.
A bit more, please?
A little bit more, please?
Feeling warm now?
Just a little bit more.
Are you shivering from the cold
or from being possessed?
Okay.
Right.
I've decided.
We're heading back to Ko Pha-ngan tomorrow.
After getting your stuff from the bungalow,
will you return to Pak Chong?
As for the latter...
let me think about it first.
You do not miss your family?
Well, I like the sea.
I love the ocean,
the fish,
the coconut trees,
and the cat.
But everyone at Adisuan Farm is missing you.
Can I return there?
Well, why not?
That is your home.
There's a bull about to gobble me up.
Then charge right back at it.
Oh...
No.
You are a teeny-tiny tiger.
You have no horns.
It is okay, you see.
If the bull really is waiting to
gobble you up,
I will be the one waving a red cape at it.
Are you scared of it?
No.
I'm simply disheartened.
It is okay
to let yourself be vulnerable sometimes.
You do not need to act tough
or carry everything
on your shoulders all the time.
It is okay to cry.
Nonsense.
Tough guys like me
don't cry.
That is not true at all.
Did you come up with that yourself,
or did someone else?
You will always be who you are,
a teeny-tiny tiger.
It's just a "tiger."
I guess it's time to go home.
Handsome guys don't stay heartbroken for long.
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫That's all, for I don't wish
to take someone's place♫
♫I'll simply be right here, always within reach♫
♫Like a gentle breeze bringing you peace♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side♫
You look stiff.
Did you get Botox or something?
I'm sorry,
but are we friends or what?
Last night, you said we should be friends.
No offense, but listen.
Just forget about last night.
You mean when you cried?
Ji.
Ra.
Nat!
What about it?
- There.
- Ow!
- Take that.
- Ouch!
- There.
- Ow!
- There!
- Ouch!
- It hurts!
- There, there, there.
- Ow, ow.
I will hit you all over!
- There!
- Why are you hitting me?
I am exorcising whatever is possessing you.
Have a taste of my palm.
- There, there, there.
- Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You got me.
- Is the ghost gone?
- Stop!
- You got me now.
- Is it gone?
The ghost will lash out
if you hit me one more time.
Well, you played along.
In case you don't know,
I am
strict!
Serious!
Intimidating!
And fearsome.
You should be respectful and scared
rather than treating me like a joke.
Understood?
I understand.
Gosh...
I was laughing at you for trying to lash out.
- Roar!
- Whoa!
There.
Hey!
That actually scared me.
Serves you right.
Take that.
One more time.
By the way...
Hm?
Once we make it to the island,
what happens next...
for us?
Sorry?
I mean...
what will you do next?
You.
What about you?
Will you return home?
What if I chose not to?
Mm...
I would probably stay here
trying to convince you for a few more days.
But eventually, I will have to go home.
I miss my cat.
Hm?
You miss your cat?
Mm.
And do you miss me?
And why do I have to miss you?
Huh?
Well, that's because
I'm a teeny-tiny tiger, aren't I?
That's basically a cat.
Meow.
Does a teeny-tiny tiger usually meow?
Mm.
Should it not be...
"beep, beep"
instead?
Hm?
What about you?
Do you honk if I squeeze you
like this?
Hm?
Beep, beep, beep.
- Beep, beep, beep.
- What are you doing?
Oh...
What is with all the beeping?
I guess I'll stop.
I guess you are still possessed.
Beep.
Beep!
Is it gone?
Is it gone now?
Beep!
Mm.
You and I
always find a way to have a laugh, don't we?
Do I also have to
accidentally trip and kiss you
for the sake of realism?
At this rate,
a kiss is a no-brainer, isn't it?
The boat's here!
Hey!
The boat is here.
Let's go. Come on.
Ow!
Oh.
Hop on my back.
Let me put on my sandals first.
I can hold them for you.
Here. Hop on.
Three, two, one.
Now!
Ow.
Ow!
Have you gained weight?
Hey!
♫Time stood still when I met you♫
♫The way you gazed at me too♫
♫Couldn't understand what I felt, I had no clue♫
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
Hey.
Hm?
- Boo!
- Whoa!
Why did you flinch?
Why did you lunge at me, then?
What?
I was going to tell you that we're here.
But you zoned out.
That's why
- I did this!
- Whoa!
Like that.
Hey.
Haven't you been
complaining about your eyes hurting?
So here we are.
Well, yes.
Him kissing me...
was it just to tease me,
or did it mean something else?
I think I should go now.
Fine.
Want me to stay with you?
That is okay.
Go for a walk in the meantime.
Well, sure.
Let's meet at the same spot.
Here.
Mm.
Bam...
This way.
Ta-da...
Woo-hoo!
Bam, bam!
Whoa...
Oh.
What a lovely pair of glasses.
So sweet.
Is that true?
I usually wear black-framed glasses.
I am not sure if this looks a bit weird.
It's true, of course.
Why would I lie?
Hm?
At any rate...
thank you
for bringing me here.
Oh, and...
Where should we go next?
This way?
Shall we?
Hm?
Which way?
You should go back to your bungalow,
and I will go back to my resort.
What is wrong?
Oh, Jam.
Why must you say such heartless things?
What seems to be the problem, Mr. Sarm?
Tell me if you need my help.
I'm scared to sleep alone.
Mind sharing your bed with me?
Uh...
Well, I'm being hunted down by someone.
And there's no honor among thieves, Jam.
What if there's more than one of them?
What if there are two,
three, four, five of them, Jam?
What if they find me,
and they kidnap me?
Where would you even find me?
Didn't you say I'm just a teeny-tiny tiger?
I'm just a little guy.
How am I supposed to fight
professional thieves?
And...
we've already slept next to each other.
So please, let me share your bed, Jam.
Uh...
Okay.
You can stay with me for now.
For real, Jam?
Mm.
Yes.
Yes!
Bam, bam!
Come on. Let's get back to your place.
I'm so sleepy right now.
Let us go.
[Uncle Mai's Kitchen]
Here.
Sarm!
Where have you been, Sarm?
Don't you know that
I've been worried sick about you?
I thought you got eaten by a shark.
Mm...
Calm down, Lantao.
I'm fine.
Not true.
You've been gone for so long.
Mm…
Well, I'm back now.
I'm not a ghost or anything.
Gosh.
Enough already, Lantao.
I'm fine.
Are you hangry?
No.
Yet your eyes say otherwise
Mr. Sarm.
Yes?
Sarm and this Japanese guy
were at each other's throats before.
So how come they're suddenly
acting so friendly today?
It feels like
they've got some sort of chemistry.
Gosh!
I'm stressing out.
Oh, Lantao.
Get me some boiled crabs.
Make it a special one.
Ten kilos.
Hey.
There's nothing going on.
I swear.
You'll feel better once you have the crabs.
Please, don't be mad.
Aww.
Aww...
Nothing's really going on.
Whoa.
Please enjoy.
This might be your last meal, Jam.
When did I ever step on your toes?
You didn't,
but you're stealing my precious one from me.
I won't let you.
You came back this time
looking all scruffy, rough, and rugged,
but somehow
you're still irresistibly handsome.
You're just as cool as always, Sarm.
Enough, Lantao.
Your dad's not here?
He's in Pak Chong right now.
Why didn't you go with him, then?
Right now, the weather's lovely there.
I'm not going there,
as I'm waiting for my heart to return.
And now, my heart
is right in front of me.
Hey.
The boy's hitting on me.
Then you might as well make your move.
I'm making a move,
but I'm not sure if this boy knows it.
You are asking the wrong person.
Tonight, I will get you on a daily talk show
so you can consult them about
your heart troubles.
Gosh.
Oh, you.
Lantao.
Are the boiled crabs ready?
It's taking too long.
We're starving to death.
My gosh.
You have to give us extra
for taking this long.
Ten kilos won't do. How about 20?
Give us your entire stock of crabs.
If you're this slow,
I'm not coming here anymore.
Is it ready yet?
What are you doing?
I am texting Mr. Sib.
He knows now that
you are being hunted down,
so we've been hopping
from island to island to escape.
Mm.
What's next?
He has called off this mission
and told me
to return the day after tomorrow,
even if I fail to bring you back.
What about me?
I want you to come with me.
Here.
Come here.
Is your foot better now?
It is.
Mr. Sarm...
This is too much.
You do not have to do this.
Don't take it off.
Is it for me?
Mm.
For what occasion, exactly?
It's for when...
you miss the person who gave it to you.
Why do you always tease me like this?
Don't forget me.
After dealing with everything here,
I'll be on my way to you.
Also, don't taunt the bull with a red cape.
It's dangerous.
Understand?
Mr. Sarm.
Hm?
Have you moved on from Mr. PiMai?
You mean forgetting him?
No.
No matter what, I'll never forget him.
Understood.
For six months,
I struggled with chronic insomnia.
My whole life was out of control.
I don't even know
when I started sleeping soundly again.
Maybe it's when
you came into my life.
Oh?!
Hup.
Mr. Sarm is no longer possessed, no?
What kind of ghost possesses him now?
You crazy guy!
Mr. Sarm.
Whoa.
You've leveled up now?
You dare insult me now?
Hm?
You're avoiding me.
I am not.
Oh?
Still refusing to admit it?
Tomorrow...
I think I am going to head back.
Okay.
See you again soon.
You and I...
Will we get to see each other again?
Of course.
Who says we won't?
You'll want to see me again, of course.
And you'll miss me a lot, too,
because there's only
one handsome guy in this world.
There are two, actually.
Is that guy as handsome as me?
And is that guy as quirky as me?
Hm?
So you know you love to act weird,
do you not?
Song is really friendly with me,
and he is very kind to me, too.
"Song is this.
Song is that."
When will you start calling me by my name?
Calling you "Mr. Sarm" is just fine.
Fine?
Who?
Who says it's fine?
It's not.
I don't like it.
You keep calling me "Mr. Sarm."
Do you know how distant
it makes me feel,
like my heart is bleeding?
You are always over the top.
Actually...
there is something
I want to apologize to you for.
It is because of me
that those guys were able to find you.
Why apologize?
What fun is there in running away all alone?
Running away with you is the way.
It's so much fun.
Did you even ask if it is for me?
It's ride or die.
You
and I.
Are you coming with me?
If yes,
blink.
Mm!
Sarm!
Whoa!
Of all times?!
There must be something going on
between Sarm and this Japanese guy,
given the way they look at each other
and how absurdly close they are.
Or...have his feelings really changed?
I can't.
Tonight, I have to find out
what Sarm really feels,
and whether Jam...
feels the same way about Sarm as I do.
I won't let anyone beat me to it,
even if it's Jam.
We'll see about that.
Let's have dinner at Uncle Mai's Kitchen.
I am not that hungry.
You go ahead and eat.
How come you're not hungry?
You haven't had anything today.
I said I am not hungry.
Oh...
You are
No. 1 when it comes to
saying one thing and feeling another.
You said you weren't hungry.
That means you want crabs.
Okay. Got it.
Let's go.
Who told you that?
You are just imagining things.
Please come with me.
I'll treat you to
as many boiled crabs as you want.
Come on.
Gosh!
I do not want to eat crabs.
I want to cook some instant noodles.
Sure thing.
If you don't want to go,
I'll carry you.
Hey!
Mr. Sarm, you crazy guy.
Huh?!
"Mr. Sarm, you crazy guy"?
I told you to call me by my name.
How dare you call me that?
Let's just go.
You have to come with me.
Now.
Come!
- Come with me now.
- Mr. Sarm...
- Go!
- I do not want to go.
- Come on!
- Let go!
Now!
Let go!
- Now!
- Oh!
Ow...
Oh...
Jam.
Oh.
Ow.
Oh...
There, there.
There!
Aww...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
I won't be so rough next time.
Feel better.
Feel no pain.
Stop it!
Whoa.
Why do you always do this?
It is not fun for me.
I'm sorry.
I won't be too rough with you again.
Please?
Let's go.
Let's have dinner together.
Let's enjoy tasty food
and crabs.
It'll put you in a better mood.
Let's go get something delicious.
Come on.
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Honestly, you...
Come on.
You always have to have your way.
There are so many moons in the sky tonight.
See?
These are not moons.
These are just some lights.
Are they?
Sarm.
Ahem!
Ahem! Ahem!
Lantao.
Yes, Sarm?
Isn't this too close?
What would you like to have tonight?
Would you like me as a snack
to go with your drink?
I'll have
some bread topped with strawberry "jam."
Do you have any?
How would we have that?
This is a seafood restaurant.
Well...
The same order as always?
Let me take care of it.
Mm.
This seafood restaurant
serves a person, too?
Gosh...
Uh...
Lantao was just teasing me.
And you had to play along, too, right?
Just joking around
like friends usually do.
You wouldn't be jealous,
would you?
Jealous?
Who's jealous?
Oh, oh?
Acting strange now, huh?
You aren't jealous, are you?
Come on, come on.
Are you?
It is not like that.
Hm?
You stubborn little thing.
You are.
You absolutely are.
Aww.
Little Jam's getting jealous.
Little Jam's getting jealous over me.
Little Jam...
Mr. Sarm!
Oh...
Waaah!
Stop that!
Ow.
Then who am I supposed to
peel these crabs for?
Oh.
The Lentao-ils are so sweet…
Mr. Sarm!
I want to head back now.
Oh.
Waaah! Little Jam!
Don't go just yet, Jam.
I got you some liquor on the house.
Let's have a little celebration
to welcome you two back.
Ah. Hey..
That's all for the celebration?
It may not be
as grand as befits your status,
but I prepared it with my little heart.
What?
May I have a drink?
One glass.
Half a glass, then.
Someone like you should never drink again.
It's only once in a while.
Just a little bit.
Please?
Just a sip, okay?
Allow me to prepare it for you.
Oh.
Mm.
How would you like yours, Jam?
Do you like it neat?
Just serve him soda.
Why can I not drink?
You can drink, too.
Oh.
Well, you're a lightweight.
Just a little bit and you're already drunk.
Who says I am?
What are you gonna do if you get drunk?
I can hold my liquor.
I used to have a drink
while listening to Mr. Sib vent.
I have even drunk through the night.
With this,
it is nothing to me.
Lantao.
Give it all you have got.
Jam, you're amazing.
Leave it to me.
Oh.
Whoa.
Here you go, Jam.
Full strength, just as you requested.
Watch and learn.
You're awesome, Jam.
You're the real deal.
Gosh...
I wish I had a handbook for cats
on how to deal with an argumentative cat
and make up with an angry one.
This one's yours, Sarm.
You're going to love how strong it is.
Ahem, ahem.
Cheers!
Ow...
So dizzy.
Hey, Little Jam.
I guess you should stop.
You're hammered.
Let go...
Hm?
I am not drunk.
Whoa.
Not drunk, huh?
Look at you.
I am just dizzy.
You are the one who is hammered.
That sobered me right up.
[Mission: Hunt Down the Teeny-tiny Tiger]
My mission was simply
to stay by Mr. Sarm's side
until he got through these hard times.
But the closer I get,
the harder it is to tell
whether he cares for me
or treats everyone this way.
I've been telling myself
not to cross the line,
not to waver, and not to
let my heart overrule my reason.
But it seems my toughest mission
isn't taking care of Mr. Sarm,
but stopping myself from falling for him.
Now that I am playing with your feelings,
are you having fun?
Jam!
Perfect timing.
You're back, aren't you?
I'd like you to come support Song.
He's a bit tied up.
No problem.
I will be there right away.
♫It seems like something's moving♫
♫What's in my heart isn't too much, but I only♫
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫That's all, for I don't wish
to take someone's place♫
♫I'll simply be right here, always within reach♫
♫Like a gentle breeze bringing you peace♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side♫
[Your Third Series]